<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Natalie&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Natalie&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>BIO311 Lab Report Gram and Acid Fast Staining</title>
      <link>/2017/10/03/bio311-lab-report-gram-and-acid-fast-staining/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Oct 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/10/03/bio311-lab-report-gram-and-acid-fast-staining/</guid>
      <description>Introduction In this lab, two types of differential staining were performed. The first was Gram staining and the second was Acid Fast. Gram staining is one of the most commonly used staining procedures in microbiology. Gram staining can characterize bacteria into two groups: gram positive bacteria or gram negative bacteria. Gram positive bacteria stain violet while gram negative bacteria stain red. This is due to the peptidoglycan layers in the bacteria; a thicker layer allows for the retention of the stain.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>CSC115 Ch5 HW Help</title>
      <link>/2017/09/28/csc115-ch5-hw-help/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 28 Sep 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/2017/09/28/csc115-ch5-hw-help/</guid>
      <description>Before beginning this assignment we must first take care of a couple housekeeping things in R.
First you must load the package TurtleGraphics
library(TurtleGraphics) Exercise 1 The Problem Using the TurtleGraphics function write a function called ‘turtle_gon()’ that draws a regular polygon. The user should be able to specify the side-length and the number of sides. Using your function draw a polygon with 12 sides, each having a length of 15 units.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>